en:
  global:
    yes: "Yes"
    no: "No"
  inputs:
    choose_a_country: "Choose a country"
  register_if_acces_to_cuesstinaire_view: "You must be registered if you want access to basic tool"
  view_report: View Report


  form:
    not_ready:
      summary: "You must complete the form before we can provide summary analysis"
      cost: "You must complete the form before we can provide cost analysis"
    value_not_set: "No answer provided"
    skip: "skip this question"
    shared:
      country:
        question: "In which country does your water service take place?"
        placeholder: "Select a country"
      capital:
        question: "How much has been/will be spent setting up the water service including construction (per person)?"
        info: "Capital Expediture (hardware): Capital invested in constructing or purchasing fixed assets such as concrete structures, pumps and pipes. Capital Expenditure (software): The costs of one-off work with stakeholders prior to construction or implementation, extension, enhancement and augmentation (including costs of one-off capacity building activities). See: http://akvopedia.org/wiki/Capital_Expenditure_(CapEx)"
      recurrent:
        question: "How much is being spent/will be spent to operate, maintain and support the delivery of water services (per person per year)?"
        info: "Operating and minor maintenance expenditure: typically comprises regular expenditure such as labour, fuel, chemicals, materials, and purchases of any bulk water. See: http://akvopedia.org/wiki/Operational_and_Minor_Maintenance_Expenditure_(OpEx) Capital maintenance expenditure: Asset renewal and replacement cost: occasional and ‘lumpy’ costs that seek to restore the functionality of a system, such as replacing pump rods or foot valves in handpumps, or a diesel generator in motorised systems. See: http://akvopedia.org/wiki/Capital_Maintenance_Expenditure_(CapManEx) Expediture of direct support: Direct support is structured support to service providers and users or user groups related to the operation and management of a WASH service; direct support costs are the costs of such support. They cover monitoring, technical advice and administrative, organisational or legal support.  The costs of support before and during the capital construction of a project are not included; they are considered to be capital software. Direct support is often used synonymously with “post-construction support”. See: http://akvopedia.org/wiki/Expenditure_Direct_Support_(ExpDS) Expenditure of indirect support: Indirect support costs cover expenditure on this macro-level support, including planning and policy making, and support to decentralised service authorities or local government. Indirect support includes capacity building for professionals and technicians and capacity support to local government as service authorities, for example to adhere to national norms, standards and guidelines. See: http://akvopedia.org/wiki/Expenditure_Indirect_Support_(ExpIDS)"
        value_label: "Per person<br/> per year"
      values:
        v0: "No service"
        v1: "Sub-standard service"
        v2: "Basic service"
        v3: "High service"
        info: "A water service level characterises the benefits that users receive, measured by a combination of four criteria; quantity of water, quality of water, accessibility, and reliability. See: http://www.washcost.info/page/2454"
      select_an_option: "Select an Option"
    water_basic:
      water:
        question: "What is the main water supply technology used?"
        answers:
          a0: "Borehole & handpump"
          a1: "Mechanised borehole"
          a2: "Single-town scheme"
          a3: "Multi-town scheme"
          a4: "Mixed-pipe supply"
        info:
          i0: "Reticulated supply with pumping, storage and distribution through public stand posts with provision for house connections."
          i1: "Water is supplied through a small distribution network and connected public stand posts. Water storage is limited, typically to an overhead storage tank  directly connected to the pump.  Household connections are rare."
          i2: "Maecenas elementum tristique nunc sed vehicula. Mauris dignissim erat ut lectus rutrum elementum. Etiam pharetra ac massa sit amet mattis. Nam blandit, nibh sed mattis accumsan, nisi risus vulputate eros, in ar laoreet."
          i3: "Reticulated supply with pumping, storage and distribution supplied to a number of interconnected towns or villages. Each village with its own storage and distribution network."
          i4: "Water is supplied through a combination of separate, often overlapping, service delivery systems."
      population:
        default_question: "How many people in this area are receiving this water service?"
        question: "How many people are served by a %{technology}?"
        value_label: "People"
        answers:
          a0: "Less than 500"
          a1: "501 - 5,000"
          a2: "5,001 - 15,000"
          a3: "More than 15,000"
        info: "Please indicate the total number of people that are meant to be using the service in the area. A water system will typically have a design population, sometimes defined by local regulations, for how many people it is meant to serve. The total number of people would be the design population of the system times the number of systems in the area. For example, if a handpump is meant to serve 300 people and there are 100 handpumps in the area, the number of people that are meant to be using the service is 30,000 people (300 people x 100 handpumps)."
      time:
        question: "How long does it take to collect water per day from these services?"
        value_label: "Minutes per day"
        answers:
          a0: "Less than 10"
          a1: "Between 10 and 30"
          a2: "Between 30 and 60"
          a3: "More than 60"
      quantity:
        question: "How much water is used from the water service?"
        value_label: "Litres per person per day"
        answers:
          a0: "Less than 5L"
          a1: "5 - 19L"
          a2: "20-60L"
          a3: "More than 60L"
      quality:
        question: "Is water quality testing done?"
        answers:
          a3: "Regular and meets standards"
          a2: "Occational and meets standards"
          a1: "One-off after construction"
          a0: "No testing"
      reliability:
        question: "How reliable is the water service?"
        answers:
          a0: "Works all the time"
          a1: "Not working less than 12 days a year"
          a2: "Not working more than 12 days a year"
          a3: "Not working all of the time"
      recurrent:
        value_label: "US$ Per person per Year"
    sanitation_basic:
      country:
        question: "In which country does your sanitation service take place?"
      recurrent:
        question: "How much is being spent/will be spent to operate, maintain and support the delivery of sanitation services (per person per year)?"
        info: "Operating and minor maintenance expenditure: typically comprises regular expenditure such as labour, fuel, chemicals, materials, and purchases of any bulk water. See: http://akvopedia.org/wiki/Operational_and_Minor_Maintenance_Expenditure_(OpEx) Capital maintenance expenditure: Asset renewal and replacement cost: occasional and ‘lumpy’ costs that seek to restore the functionality of a system, such as replacing pump rods or foot valves in handpumps, or a diesel generator in motorised systems. See: http://akvopedia.org/wiki/Capital_Maintenance_Expenditure_(CapManEx) Expediture of direct support: Direct support is structured support to service providers and users or user groups related to the operation and management of a WASH service; direct support costs are the costs of such support. They cover monitoring, technical advice and administrative, organisational or legal support.  The costs of support before and during the capital construction of a project are not included; they are considered to be capital software. Direct support is often used synonymously with “post-construction support”. See: http://akvopedia.org/wiki/Expenditure_Direct_Support_(ExpDS) Expenditure of indirect support: Indirect support costs cover expenditure on this macro-level support, including planning and policy making, and support to decentralised service authorities or local government. Indirect support includes capacity building for professionals and technicians and capacity support to local government as service authorities, for example to adhere to national norms, standards and guidelines. See: http://akvopedia.org/wiki/Expenditure_Indirect_Support_(ExpIDS)"
        value_label: "Per person<br/> per year"
      household:
        question: "What is the typical household size?"
      latrine:
        question: "What type of latrine technology is being used?"
        answers:
          a0: "Traditional pit latrine"
          a1: "Slab latrine"
          a2: "Vip latrine"
          a3: "Pour Flush Latrine"
          a4: "Twin Pit Pour Flush Latrine"
          a5: "Latrine with septic tank"
      population:
        question: "How many people in this area are receiving this sanitation service?"
        value_label: "People"
      providing:
        question: "Does the service provide latrines at the household level?"
        answers:
          a0: "Yes"
          a1: "No"
      impermeability:
        question: "Does the latrine have an impermeable slab?"
        answers:
          a0: "Impermeable slab"
          a1: "No impermeable slab"
        info: "This can be a traditional pit latrine with an impermeable slab (made from local materials, a pit latrine with a concrete impermeable slab, or a pour-flush or septic tank latrines, often with a concrete or bricked lines pit/tank with sealed impermeable slab."
      environment:
        question: "What is the environmental impact of the service?"
        answers:
          a0: "Non problematic + safe disposal + re-use of bi-products "
          a1: "Non problematic +safe disposal"
          a2: "Significant pollution"
      usage:
        question: "Which family members use the latrine?"
        answers:
          a0: "All"
          a1: "Some"
          a2: "None"
      reliability:
        question: "Is the latrine cleaned and emptied when required?"
        answers:
          a0: "Yes"
          a1: "Not consistently"
          a2: "No"
      recurrent:
        question: "How much is being spent/will be spent to operate, maintain and support the delivery of sanitation services (per person per year)?"
        value_label: "US$ Per person per Year"

